[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "M16 is the U.S. military designation for a family of rifles that had a field trial in the early 1960s in what war?", "correct_answer": "Vietnam War", "incorrect_answers": ["Civil War", "Gulf War", "Korean War"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the Damper bread variety originate?", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "India", "Mexico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This freshwater mammal, found only in the Yangtze River, is the most endangered (even possibly extinct) cetacean and one of the most endangered species in the world.", "correct_answer": "Chinese River Dolphin", "incorrect_answers": ["Ganges River Dolphin", "La Plata Dolphin", "Amazon River Dolphin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the fourth installment in the Die Hard series?", "correct_answer": "Live Free or Die Hard", "incorrect_answers": ["Die Hard with a Vengeance", "None of these", "Die Hard with a Revenge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the girl next to you orders baled hay, life preserver and java for breakfast, what has she ordered?", "correct_answer": "Shredded wheat, donut and coffee", "incorrect_answers": ["Cream of wheat , donut and coffee", "Hash browns, omelet, and coffee", "Buckwheat pancakes, danish, and coffee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ancient Roman Empire stretched from modern day Great Britain to Egypt. Which present day country was not part of the Roman Empire?", "correct_answer": "Poland", "incorrect_answers": ["Tunisia", "Turkey", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When James Bond is invited to play this sport, in 1965s, Thunderball, he remarks that he knows more about women, than about this sport.", "correct_answer": "Shooting clay pigeons", "incorrect_answers": ["Tennis", "Horse riding", "Archery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of these roof types, which one is least likely to have gables?", "correct_answer": "Hipped Roof", "incorrect_answers": ["Pitched Roof", "Gambrel Roof", "Cat Slide Roof"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which decade were sneakers, or tennis shoes invented?", "correct_answer": "1830s", "incorrect_answers": ["1940s", "1890s", "1920s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the crime-solving cat hero of the Rita Mae Brown books?", "correct_answer": "Mrs. Murphy", "incorrect_answers": ["Old Deuteronomy", "Tucker Tee", "Mama Morton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these movies did Scarlett Johansson have a minor role in 1997?", "correct_answer": "Home Alone 3", "incorrect_answers": ["Home Alone 4", "Home Alone 2", "Home Alone 1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A rook is worth more than a bishop.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]